Guide to the Bob Wethern Papers 1900-2006
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 2: The Waterfowler's Pacific Flyway (TWPF), 1953-2003
  - "Active Eastern Oregon," 1986 (Box 29, Folder 293)
  - Eastern Oregon, 1975-1982 (Box 29, Folder 294)
  - Josephine County, OR, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 295)
  - Union County, OR, 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 296)
  - Union County, OR, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 297)
  - Lake County, OR, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 298)
  - Lake County, OR, 1986-1988 (Box 30, Folder 299)
  - Sherman County, OR, 1986-1988 (Box 30, Folder 300)
  - Jefferson County, OR, circa 1985-1990 (Box 30, Folder 301)
  - Harney County, OR, background, 1986-1988 (Box 30, Folder 302)
  - Malheur County, OR, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 303)
  - Wallowa County, OR, 1981-1990 (Box 30, Folder 304)
  - Wasco County, OR, 1980-1981 (Box 30, Folder 305)
  - Crook County, OR, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 306)
  - Morrow County, OR, circa 1985-1990 (Box 30, Folder 307)
  - Umatilla County, OR, 1981-1987 (Box 30, Folder 308)
  - Deschutes County, OR, 1982-1987 (Box 30, Folder 309)
  - Bully Creek Gun Club, Hood River, OR, 1953 and 1990 (Box 30, Folder 310)
  - Harvey Fischer, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 311)
  - Elsie Halsten, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 312)
  - "Hank Helber, Dave and Boys," 1983 (Box 31, Folder 313)
  - J. David "Skip" Hosfield (OR), 1998-1999 (Box 31, Folder 314)
  - Kittredge-Claggett (interview transcripts), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 315)
  - McPhillips information, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 316)
  - "Rutherford-Pengally duplications," 1986-1988 (Box 31, Folder 317)
  - Lee Perkins, notes and drafts, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 318)
  - "Borderline," 1984-1988 (Box 31, Folder 319)
  - Miscellaneous items, Washington and Oregon, 1985-1990 (Box 31, Folder 320)
  - Western Washington (includes partial TWPF manuscript section: Waterways and Wetlands of Western Washington), 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 321)
  - Clark County, WA, 1984-1987 (Box 31, Folder 322)
  - Skamania County, WA, 1984-1986 (Box 31, Folder 323)
  - Cowlitz County, WA, 1980-1987 (Box 31, Folder 324)
  - Lewis County, WA, 1979-1987 (Box 31, Folder 325)
  - Pacific County, WA, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 326)
  - Pacific County, WA, 1984-1986 (Box 31, Folder 327)
  - Grays Harbor County, WA, 1983-1987 (Box 32, Folder 328)
  - Grays Harbor County, WA (also includes some Pacific County material), 1983-1986 (Box 32, Folder 329)
  - Grays Harbor County, WA, 1983-1986 (Box 32, Folder 330)
  - Thurston County, WA, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 331)
  - Tacoma-Nisqually (WA) "backups," 1984-1987 (Box 32, Folder 332)
  - Nisqually Farms (WA) photographs and notes, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 333)
  - Nisqually River delta, WA, 1985-1987 (Box 32, Folder 334)
  - Pierce County and Tacoma, WA, 1982-1987 (Box 32, Folder 335)
  - Mason County, WA, 1977-1987 (Box 32, Folder 336)
  - Mason County, WA, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 337)
  - TWPF manuscript section, "Waterways and Wetlands of Western Washington: Coast and Hood Canal Only," 1991 (Box 32, Folder 338)
  - TWPF manuscript section, "Waterways and Wetlands of Western Washington: Coast and Hood Canal Only" (continued) (Box 33, Folder 339)
  - Coast and Hood Canal (WA). Includes TWPF manuscript section, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 340)
  - Upper Olympic Peninsula, WA, 1981-1987 (Box 33, Folder 341)
  - Kitsap County, WA (includes some North Mason County), 1980-1986 (Box 33, Folder 342-343)
  - Seattle, WA, 1980-1986 (Box 33, Folder 344)
  - King County, Seattle area, WA, 1973-1987 (Box 33, Folder 345)
  - King County, WA, 1983-1987 (Box 34, Folder 346)
  - Clallam County, WA, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 347)
  - Clallam and Jefferson Counties, WA, 1987-1988 (Box 34, Folder 348)
  - Jefferson and Clallam Counties, WA, 1984-1986 (Box 34, Folder 349)
  - Island County, WA, 1981-1987 (Box 34, Folder 350)
  - Clallam and San Juan Counties, WA, 1983-1987 (Box 34, Folder 351)
  - Snohomish County, WA, 1985-1987 (Box 34, Folder 352)
  - Skagit County, WA, 1985-1987 (Box 34, Folder 353)
  - Skagit County, WA, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 354)
  - Whatcom and Skagit counties, WA, 1983-1987 (Box 34, Folder 355)
  - Whatcom County, WA, 1985-1986 (Box 34, Folder 356)
  - Skagit County, WA, "duplicates and backups," 1985-1986 (Box 34, Folder 357)
  - Edison, WA (includes versions of TWPF manuscript section and notes on Edison hunting lodge), 1985-1987 (Box 35, Folder 358-359)
  - Padilla Bay, WA,1980-1988 (Box 35, Folder 360)
  - Upper Puget Trough (WA). Includes TWPF manuscript section, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 361-362)
  - King County to Columbia River (WA). Includes TWPF manuscript section, circa 1985-1990 (Box 35, Folder 363-364)
  - TWPF manuscript sections, circa 1985-1990 (Box 35, Folder 365)
  - Western Washington: Upper Puget Trough
  - Coastal Alaska
  - "Flyway Opus," 1986-1991 (Box 36, Folder 366)
  - Miscellaneous (WA), 1982-1985 (Box 36, Folder 367)
  - Eastern Washington, 1980-1988 (Box 36, Folder 368-369)
  - "Mid-East Washington," 1980-1986 (Box 36, Folder 370-371)
  - Klickitat County, WA, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 372)
  - Yakima Valley, 1983-1986 (Box 36, Folder 373)
  - Yakima Valley, 1983-1986 (continued) (Box 37, Folder 374-375)
  - Eastern Washington (mostly Yakima), 1975-1986 (Box 37, Folder 376)
  - Brown's Farm Club (WA), 1986-1987 (Box 37, Folder 377)
  - Grays Marsh (Sequim, WA), 1984-1989 (Box 37, Folder 378)
  - Grays Marsh (WA), 1986-1994 (Box 37, Folder 379)
  - Greenhead Club (OR), 1984 (Box 37, Folder 380)
  - Oscar A. Kuppler, 1983-1984 (Box 37, Folder 381)
  - Laidlaw Island Hunting Club (WA), 1983-1986 (Box 37, Folder 382)
  - Nisqually Gun Club (WA), undated (Box 38, Folder 383)
  - Nisqually Gun Club (WA), 1977-1986 (Box 38, Folder 384)
  - Swinomish (WA) Gun Club, 1984-1986 (Box 38, Folder 385)
  - Swinomish Club (WA), 2003 (Box 38, Folder 386)
  - Bob Miller correspondence and related material (WA), 1988 (Box 38, Folder 387)
  - Fred Nist ("Mr. Duck"), 1984 (Box 38, Folder 388)
  - William K. Ryan and John E. Ryan, Jr., 1983-1984 (Box 38, Folder 389)
  - John Spellman (and other Washington State governors), 1983 (Box 38, Folder 390)
  - George Twining, 1988-1991 (Box 38, Folder 391)
  - Ira Yeager, Washington lakes, and miscellaneous, 1988-1989 (Box 38, Folder 392)
  - Statistical information and miscellaneous, 1984-1986 (Box 38, Folder 393)
  - Miscellaneous (WA, AK, BC), 1981-1988 (Box 38, Folder 394)
  - Miscellaneous (WA, AK, Canada), 1981-1988 (Box 38, Folder 395)
  - Alaska and British Columbia, 1987-1988 (Box 38, Folder 396)
  - Leigh S. Stevenson (BC), 1980-1987 (Box 38, Folder 397)
  - British Columbia "used," 1980-1989 (Box 38, Folder 398)
  - British Columbia. Includes TWPF manuscript section: Vancouver Island, 1980-1990 (Box 39, Folder 399)
  - Coastal British Columbia. Includes TWPF manuscript section, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 400)
  - Canada and Alaska history, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 401)
  - Alaska and Canada miscellaneous (folder 403 includes a manuscript account of Wethern and David Hagerbaumer's 1988 visit to Barrow, AK), 1976-1989 (Box 39, Folder 402-404)
  - "Miscellaneous Flyway" (mostly Alaska), 1984-2003 (Box 39, Folder 405)
  - Alaska (includes TWPF manuscript section), 1982-1989 (Box 39, Folder 406-407)
  - Alaska, 1977-1986 (Box 40, Folder 408)
  - Alaska, 1980-1989 (Box 40, Folder 409-410)
  - Alaska (includes TWPF manuscript section; also some Alberta material), 1982-1989 (Box 40, Folder 411)
  - Alaska, 1986-1988 (Box 40, Folder 412-413)
  - Point Barrow, AK, 1982-1988 (Box 40, Folder 414)
  - Barrow, AK, 1987-1988 (Box 41, Folder 415)
  - TWPF manuscript section: Alaska, circa 1985-1990 (Box 41, Folder 416-420)
  - Birds of Arctic Alaska, circa 1985-1990 (Box 41, Folder 421)
  - Alaska exploration and duck hunting, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 422-423)
  - Gren Collins interview, notes, correspondence, 1968-1988 (Box 41, Folder 424-425)
  - Bob Henning, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 426)
  - New Mexico, circa 1985-1990 (Box 41, Folder 427)
  - Texas, circa 1985-1990 (Box 42, Folder 428)
  - Texas, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 429)
  - New Mexico, circa 1985-1990 (Box 42, Folder 430)
  - Arizona, 1978-1986 (Box 42, Folder 431)
  - Utah, 1981-1989 (Box 42, Folder 432)
  - Chesapeake Duck Club (UT), 1983-1988 (Box 42, Folder 433)
  - Nevada, 1964-1986 (Box 42, Folder 434)
  - "Active" Colorado file, 1983-1987 (Box 42, Folder 435)
  - Colorado, 1985-1989 (Box 43, Folder 436)
  - Wyoming (also includes some Alaska material), 1980-1990 (Box 43, Folder 437-440)
  - "Active" Idaho file, 1985-1988 (Box 43, Folder 441)
  - Idaho, 1981-1987 (Box 43, Folder 442-444)
  - J. H. Gipson diary and photographs (Salmon River, ID), 1986 (Box 43, Folder 445)
  - "Active" Montana file, 1986-1987 (Box 43, Folder 446)
  - Montana, circa 1985-1990 (Box 43, Folder 447)
  - Montana, 1989-1990 (Box 43, Folder 448)
  - Alberta, 1981-1987 (Box 44, Folder 449)
  - Bow River (Alberta), 1980-1982 (Box 44, Folder 450)
  - Alberta, 1983-1985 (Box 44, Folder 451)
  - Yukon, 1984-1985 (Box 44, Folder 452)
  - Far North Inland--Yukon (research materials and partial TWPF manuscript section, "Far North Phase of Inland Corridor Section"), 1983 (Box 44, Folder 453)
  - Inland Corridor, 1987-1991 (Box 44, Folder 454)
  - Inland Corridor, 1983-1991 (Box 44, Folder 455-456)
  - Inland Corridor (Oregon), 1980-1990 (Box 44, Folder 457)
  - Miscellaneous (includes printed reproductions of watercolor illustrations, information about the Brandt Club, and a file labeled "Battle of Sexes"), 1976-2000 (Box 44, Folder 458)
  - Updates and edits for TWPF manuscript (correspondence and interview transcripts, multiple areas), 1989-1991 (Box 45, Folder 459)
  - Pacific Northwest maps (printed maps, some with annotations, circa 1969-1985 (Box 45, Folder 460)
  - TWPF general background, 1986-1991 (Box 45, Folder 461)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence and transcript of 1986 interview with Darrell Palmer, 1986-1990 (Box 45, Folder 462)
  - "TWPF reconsidered," 1987 (Box 45, Folder 463)
  - TWPF correspondence, 1977-1986 (Box 45, Folder 464)
  - Statistics (waterfowl distribution, harvesting, etc.), 1971-1986 (Box 45, Folder 465)
  - "Updating Needs," 1986-1988 (Box 45, Folder 466)
  - Jerry Bicknell, 1983-1988 (Box 45, Folder 467)
  - Countrysport Press, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 468)
  - James Gerstley, "The Borax Years" (photocopy) and insertions, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 469)
  - David Godine (mainly correspondence with Godine and others related to publication of TWPF), 1987-1989 (Box 45, Folder 470)
  - Game and Gun magazine (mainly correspondence related to article publication), 1989-1995 (Box 45, Folder 471)
  - David Hagerbaumer, 1973-1988 (Box 46, Folder 472)
  - Bob Henning (mostly WA and AK), 1987-1991 (Box 46, Folder 473-475)
  - R.E. Saylor gunning logs, 1983-1985 (Box 46, Folder 476)
  - Flyway project correspondence, notes, drafts of introduction; 1989-1995 (Box 46, Folder 477)
  - Oral histories (mainly photocopies of transcripts related to Idaho), 1980-1982 (Box 46, Folder 478-480)
  - Sporting goods store art, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 481)
  - Miscellaneous TWPF, 1985-1989 (Box 46, Folder 482)
  - "Miscellaneous TWPF resources," 1974-1989 (Box 47, Folder 483)
  - Miscellaneous items, circa 1985-1990 (Box 47, Folder 484)
  - Miscellaneous California gun club notes, circa 1985-1990 (Box 47, Folder 485)
  - Miscellaneous (correspondence and interview transcript), 1982-1987 (Box 47, Folder 486)
  - Miscellaneous; 1999, undated (Box 47, Folder 487)
  - Miscellaneous (photocopies and photographs), circa 1985-1990 (Box 47, Folder 488)
- Series 3: Photographs, 1900-1990 (bulk 1979-1990)
  - Scrapbook (mainly photographs with Wethern's captions), 1985-1987 (Box 47, Folder 489-490)
  - "Flyway Special Pix" (photographs, correspondence, and miscellaneous), 1981-1993 (Box 47, Folder 491)
  - Western Pacific Flyway, circa 1985-1990 (Box 47, Folder 492)
  - Southern California (includes related documentation), 1981-1986 (Box 47, Folder 493)
  - Northern California clubs (photographs), circa 1985-1990 (Box 47, Folder 494)
  - Oregon, Washington, California, circa 1985-1990 (Box 48, Folder 495)
  - Oregon, circa 1985-1990 (Box 48, Folder 496)
  - Lower Columbia River duck shack and waterfowling photographs (includes related documentatation), circa 1970s-1980s (Box 48, Folder 497)
  - Hunting and fishing (mainly WA and OR), circa 1985-1990 (Box 48, Folder 498)
  - Oregon, Washington, and some other locations, circa 1985-1990 (Box 48, Folder 499)
  - Washington, circa 1985-1990 (Box 48, Folder 500)
  - Washington (also miscellaneous or unidentified), circa 1985-1990 (Box 48, Folder 501)
  - Marcus Nalley's duck club at mouth of Skokomish River, Mason County, WA (photographs and notes), circa 1985-1990 (Box 48, Folder 502)
  - San Juan Farms photographs, circa 1985-1990 (Box 48, Folder 503)
  - Skagit Packers (for TCT), circa 1985-1990 (Box 48, Folder 504)
  - Canadian waterfowling, circa 1985-1990 (Box 48, Folder 505)
  - British Columbia (includes related documentation), 1982-1985 (Box 48, Folder 506)
  - British Columbia, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 507)
  - Alaska (photocopies; includes related documentation), 1983 (Box 48, Folder 508)
  - Arizona, circa 1985-1990 (Box 49, Folder 509)
  - Utah (includes related documentation), 1982-1983 (Box 49, Folder 510)
  - Nevada, circa 1985-1990 (Box 49, Folder 511)
  - Wyoming, circa 1985-1990 (Box 49, Folder 512)
  - Idaho (includes related documentation), 1982-1983 (Box 49, Folder 513)
  - Montana (includes related documentation), circa 1985-1990 (Box 49, Folder 514)
  - Montana, 1900 (Box 49, Folder 515)
  - Alberta, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 516)
  - Yukon Territory (includes related documentation), 1979 (Box 49, Folder 517)
  - Hunting and fishing photographs and notes, circa 1985-1990 (Box 49, Folder 518)
  - Miscellaneous (photocopies; includes related documentation), circa 1985-1990 (Box 49, Folder 519)
  - Miscellaneous, circa 1985-1990 (Box 49, Folder 520)
  - Processing files (includes Wethern obituaries and tributes) (Box 49, Folder 521-522)
- Series 4: Index card file and computer diskettes, circa 1980-1990
  - Computer diskettes (sixteen 8 inch floppy disks) with word processing files in unknown format, 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 523-527)